<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Adam Boscarino</title><link>https://adam.boscarino.me/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Adam Boscarino</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://adam.boscarino.me/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Apache Airflow at Devoted Health</title><link>https://adam.boscarino.me/posts/airflow-at-devoted-health/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://adam.boscarino.me/posts/airflow-at-devoted-health/</guid><description>Apache Airflow is an open-source workflow orchestration tool. There are many posts available that explain the core concepts of Airflow (I recommend this one). This post assumes you have some familiarity with these concepts and focuses on how we develop, test, and deploy Airflow and Airflow DAGs at Devoted Health. Devoted is a Medicare Advantage startup aimed at making healthcare easier, more affordable, and believes every member should be treated like we would treat a member of our own family.</description></item><item><title>Introducing dag-factory</title><link>https://adam.boscarino.me/posts/introducing-dag-factory/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://adam.boscarino.me/posts/introducing-dag-factory/</guid><description>Apache Airflow is &amp;ldquo;a platform to programmatically author, schedule, and monitor workflows.&amp;rdquo; And it is currently having its moment. At DataEngConf NYC 2018, it seemed like every other talk was either about or mentioned Airflow. There have also been countless blog posts about how different companies are using the tool and it even has a podcast!
A major use case for Airflow seems to be ETL or ELT or ETTL or whatever acronym we are using today for moving data in batches from production systems to data warehouses.</description></item></channel></rss>